(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.2",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Thank you all for joining us today
for Hakos Baelz's Birthday Live 2026.
Before we begin, I have a few
requests and reminders for everyone.
Feel free to enjoy food and drinks
in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone,
but please be careful not to spill
anything on your keyboard.
The official hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D.
Please post about us on social media.
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone
during the show is more than welcome.
We'd love it if you could share them online
to help spread the excitement.
The show will begin shortly,
so please stay tuned.
皆様、本日はハコス・ベールズ 生誕祭 2026に
Everyone, thank you so much for joining us today
お越しくださいまして、誠にありがとうございます。
for Hakos Baelz's Birthday Live 2026.
開演に先立ちまして、
皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
Before the show begins, I have some
requests and information to share with you.
テレビやパソコン、スマートフォンの前では
飲食は可能ですが、
Eating and drinking in front of your
TV, PC, or smartphone is allowed,
キーボードにこぼさないように気をつけてください。
but please be careful not to
spill anything on your keyboard.
当配信のハッシュタグは #ReCOLOR3D です。
SNSでたくさんポストしてください。
The hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D.
Please post a lot about us on social media.
開演中、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる
写真撮影は大歓迎です。
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone
during the performance is more than welcome.
たくさんポストして盛り上がってくださいますと幸いです。
We would appreciate it if you could
post a lot and help build the excitement.
それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Now then, please wait a moment
until the show begins.
Thank you all for joining us today
for Hakos Baelz's Birthday Live 2026.
Before we begin, I have a few
requests and reminders for everyone.
Feel free to enjoy food and drinks
in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone,
but please be careful not to spill
anything on your keyboard.
The official hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D.
Please post about us on social media.
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone
during the show is more than welcome.
We'd love it if you could share them online
to help spread the excitement.
The show will begin shortly,
so please stay tuned.
皆様、本日はハコス・ベールズ 生誕祭 2026に
Everyone, thank you so much for joining us today
お越しくださいまして、誠にありがとうございます。
for Hakos Baelz's Birthday Live 2026.
開演に先立ちまして、
皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
Before the show begins, I have some
requests and information to share with you.
テレビやパソコン、スマートフォンの前では
飲食は可能ですが、
Eating and drinking in front of your
TV, PC, or smartphone is allowed,
キーボードにこぼさないように気をつけてください。
but please be careful not to
spill anything on your keyboard.
当配信のハッシュタグは #ReCOLOR3D です。
SNSでたくさんポストしてください。
The hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D.
Please post a lot about us on social media.
開演中、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる
写真撮影は大歓迎です。
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone
during the performance is more than welcome.
たくさんポストして盛り上がってくださいますと幸いです。
We would appreciate it if you could
post a lot and help build the excitement.
それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Now then, please wait a moment
until the show begins.
winning the soul
[Title: winning the soul]
光の速さで駆け抜ける衝動は
An urge to run through at the speed of light
何を犠牲にしても叶えたい強さの覚悟
Is the determination to make it come true at any cost
(no fear) 一度きりの
(no fear) It only comes once
(trust you) この瞬間に
(trust you) For this moment
賭けてみろ 自分を信じて
Bet it, trusting yourself
時には運だって必要と言うのなら
If someone tells me you need luck as well sometimes
宿命の旋律も引き寄せてみせよう
I'll draw fate as well
走れ今を まだ終われない
Run now, I can't end it yet
辿り着きたい場所があるから
There's a place I want to get to
その先へと進め
Go beyond
涙さえも強く胸に抱きしめ
Holding onto even the tears tightly
そこから始まるストーリー
A story begins from there
果てしなく続く
It goes on endlessly
winning the soul
掴め今を 変えたいなら
Grab it now if you want to change
描いた夢を未来に掲げ
Raise the future you imagined
恐れないで挑め
Don't be afraid and go
走れ今を まだ終われない
Run now, I can't end it yet
辿り着きたい場所があるから
There's a place I want to get to
その先へと進め
Go beyond
涙さえも強く胸に抱きしめ
Holding onto even the tears tightly
そこから始まるストーリー
A story begins from there
果てしなく続く
It goes on endlessly
winning the soul
woh woh woh
W-w-w-what's up everyone!
I am Chaos, the End of Events,
a steel rat trapped in a cage of ice,
your best friend Bae...
Hakos Baelz from Hololive English Promise!
ヴァルフェス、終わりの果て、THE END...
Valfes, the end of the end, THE END...
降臨の二十四時、黄金のバラ。
The 24th hour of advent, the golden rose.
汝の魂、ホロライブEnglishのハコス・ベールズです！
I am Hakos Baelz of Hololive English!
Witness me!
Ah... another year, another not-birthday live!
Thank you so much for coming everyone!
Did you like the opening act? The opening show?
This year, we have a
not-birthday birthday live again,
called ReCOLOR 3D!
That is also the hashtag, please use it! #ReCOLOR3D.
Um, I don't know, it might be...
The theme this year was "color" for many reasons.
There's also a lot of special things that are happening today,
as you may or may not already know.
There's a lot of "new" things being revealed in this live.
Maybe a new song? Maybe a new outfit?
You're just gonna have to wait and see!
えっと、今年も誕生日じゃない
Um, this year too, I'm doing a
誕生日ライブ...
"not-birthday" birthday live...
やりたいと思います。みんな来てくれてありがとう！
...is what I'm thinking. Thank you all for coming!
今日のライブでね、新しいものいっぱいあると思いますので、
There will be lots of new things in today's live,
最後まで見てくれたら嬉しいです！
so I'd be happy if you watched until the end!
あー、もう疲れてる。やばい。
Ah, I'm already tired. This is bad.
ハッシュタグも、ぜひぜひいっぱい
Please post lots of comments and photos
コメントと写真をポストしてください！
with the hashtag!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
Um... it is my birthday... not-birthday!
But I'm just so excited to be able to share this day with all of you.
Once I catch my breath,
we're gonna get this party started, yeah?
じゃあ、最後まで楽しんでください！
Well then, please enjoy until the end!
次の曲、別のステージに行くので、
For the next song, I'm going to another stage,
So I'm going to go to the other stage for the next song.
So I'll see you guys there, alright?
I'm gonna go now. Is that alright? Okay, bye!
See you guys there!
Race you!
ハッ！
Ha!
G4L
[Lyrics: q*Left Music: Giga]
[Song: G4L]
あれが正解なんで
That this is the world...
誰の成れの果て？
...just a shadow of someone?
（なんだっての悶々々）
(What is it, this constant agony?)
答えも欲しいのも 一個てくれだけ
Answers, desires, just give me one.
悩んだってしょうがないじゃんね
It’s no use worrying about it, right?
あれは夢だったって思うくにしたって
Even if I try to think it was just a dream...
（つらお）
(So painful.)
でも全然思えないんだけど
...I can't believe it at all.
助けてよ、フォロワー！
Save me, followers!
抗うだけ
Just struggling.
若さに負け
Losing to youth.
ネクストウネクストウ、lucky lucky lucky
Next to next to, lucky lucky lucky.
（オーエーオー）割り切れたらさ
(O-A-O) If I could just let it go...
（オーエーオー）楽なのにとか
(O-A-O) ...it would be so much easier.
（アハアー）もうヤダ〜
(A-ha-ah) I'm so over this!
なんていう新世界か？
What kind of new world is this?
あんた以外は…
Other than you...
あんた以外はいらない（ないない）
...I don't need anyone but you. (No, no.)
はらないでよバリア
Don't put up a barrier.
あるはずなの何か
There must be something.
あったならばハッピー！ジャンピン！（yeah）
If it's there, then Happy! Jumpin'! (Yeah!)
あんたのその手とあたしのこの手を
If your hand and my hand...
つないだらもう二度と離さないを
...intertwine, I'll never let go again.
あんたのその手があたしのこの手を
If your hand...
掴んだら、以後お見知りおきを！my love
...grabs mine, then please remember me! My love.
これで終わりなんて
That this is the end...
あかれないままなんて（鳴いちゃってポンポンポン）
...without even opening up. (Crying out, pon-pon-pon.)
どうにかなっちゃえって願って願って
Wishing and wishing for something to happen.
ねぇ、朝帰りしたりしちゃわんじゃ？
Hey, aren't we coming home in the morning?
なあもう我慢できんpain
Man, I can't take this pain anymore.
pain痛いってばeveryday
Pain, it hurts every day.
ま、ゆうていけるけどなブルベ夏
Well, I say that, but I'm a cool-toned summer.
なんで関係ないな
Why does it even matter?
誰よりも猫
More cat-like than anyone.
節操ない、も結構
Lack of restraint is fine too.
あーしはあーしだ見といてよready
I am who I am, just watch me, ready?
もう今日で終わらせたいなって
I want to end it all today.
リスタートできたらって
Wishing I could just restart.
でも無理よもうぅぁぁ
But it's impossible now, aah!
what's on your mind？
What's on your mind?
（オーエーオー）割り切れたらさ
(O-A-O) If I could just let it go...
（オーエーオー）楽なのにとか
(O-A-O) ...it would be so much easier.
（アハアー）もうヤダ〜
(A-ha-ah) I'm so over this!
なんていう新世界か？
What kind of new world is this?
あんた以外は…
Other than you...
あんた以外はいらない（ないない）
...I don't need anyone but you. (No, no.)
はらないでよバリア
Don't put up a barrier.
あるはずなの何か
There must be something.
あったならばハッピー！ジャンピン！（yeah）
If it's there, then Happy! Jumpin'! (Yeah!)
あんたのその手とあたしのこの手を
If your hand and my hand...
つないだらもう二度と離さないを
...intertwine, I'll never let go again.
あんたのその手があたしのこの手を
If your hand...
掴んだら、以後お見知りおきを！my love
...grabs mine, then please remember me! My love.
お見知りおきを！my love
Please remember me! My love.
CR詠ZY
[Lyrics, Music: 梅とら]
[Song: CR詠ZY]
[Lyrics, Music: Umetora]
ラリラリラッタ ラリラ
Ladi ladi ladi da ladi da.
ヘイ！
Hey!
Breakaway breakaway cyber level
あのに本方位譲れてる
Giving in to those two directions...
姿しぐさ滑稽でしょ
...my appearance and gestures are ridiculous, right?
Don’t you think? Don’t you think?
I'm so lazy 多分疎外感
I’m so lazy, probably just a sense of alienation...
並べてるだけの日々
...in these days of just lining things up.
Crash crash 剥製
Crash, crash, like a stuffed specimen.
Don’t you think? Don’t you think?
In this world この頭には
In this world, inside this head...
What a beautiful mind 散る花びら
...what a beautiful mind, falling petals.
バラライカ 飲み干したいな
I want to drink up that Balalaika.
ラリラリラッタ ラリラ
Ladi ladi ladi da ladi da.
ヘイ！
Hey!
誰もがダイ
Everyone dies...
C-R-A-Z-Y
一瞬の感情に
To a momentary emotion...
Ride on ride on ride on ride on
ヘイ！
Hey!
心はナイ
There is no heart...
狂気のサムライ
...a samurai of madness.
ヘイ！
Hey!
血走る正体不明で
With bloodshot eyes, unidentified...
Fly fly ready to die
暁は昇り あなたの空
The dawn rises, your sky...
真っ赤な空
...a pitch-red sky.
粗々しく引き千切って
Violently tearing it apart.
ほらその場所で
Look, in that place...
聞こえてくる事の仕掛け
...the mechanism of what you hear.
轟くのは己の調べ
What thunders is your own melody...
誰かのじゃない己の調べ
...not someone else's, but your own.
Rat-ta-ta-ta-ta
目の前に広がる世界はブルー
The world spreading before my eyes is blue...
ひとまずさあ Move move
...for now, come on, move, move.
Big bang! 行ったれ
Big bang! Go for it.
There’s no need 何そんな張り切って偉そうに
There’s no need to be so eager and acting all high and mighty.
君もアイを 右も左も
You too, with love, right and left...
知りもしないで言わないで
...don't say things without even knowing.
Don’t you think? Don’t you think?
にやり 影が笑う
A grin, as the shadow laughs.
ヘイ！
Hey!
世界はダイ
The world dies...
C-R-A-Z-Y
繰り返すように
As if repeating...
Ride on ride on ride on ride on
ヘイ！
Hey!
分かってない
You don't understand...
あれこれよと 歌う
...singing about this and that.
Tell me something for the new
偉大な期待の時代の Vibe
The vibe of an era of great expectations
Clap back
Move my mind, and shooting my star
Favorite あなたのその瞬間
Favorite, that moment of yours
Maybe nothing wrong, nothing wrong
Lali lali la da, lali lali la da
Hey! 誰もが砕いた
Hey! Everyone crushed it
Hey! C-R-A-Z-Y
Hey! 一瞬の感情に Right on, right on, right on
Hey! On a momentary emotion, right on, right on, right on
Hey! 心は 95
Hey! My heart is 95
Hey! 陽気なサムライ
Hey! A cheerful samurai
Hey! 血走らせた目で 低空飛行 Ready to die?
Hey! With bloodshot eyes, flying low, ready to die?
Hello! 日は上り
Hello! The sun rises
あなたの空は 真っ赤な空
Your sky is a deep red sky
あらあら、地平切り裂いて
My, my, tearing through the horizon
ほら、その場所で
Look, at that place
聞こえてくる 言葉仕掛け
Word tricks can be heard
驚くのは誰？ これから まだこれから
Who will be surprised? From now on, it's still just beginning
あの街目指して
Aiming for that city
時計の針 0時の街
Clock hands, the city at midnight
猛々しくいざ Raise your voice
Bravely now, raise your voice
ほら、すぐそこで
Look, right there
始まりだす 心の宴
The heart's banquet begins
奏でるのは 誰の調べ
Whose melody is being played?
唯一無二の誰の調べ
Whose one-of-a-kind melody?
美人
[Song: Bijin (Beauty)]
美 美 美にしろ注意
Be-be-beauty, be careful
あいつの信者は多い
They have a lot of followers
己を知りなさい bitch
Know yourself, bitch
HD で魅えるのに
Even though it's visible in HD
私もあなた様みたいになりたい
Oh, I want to look like you
教えて教えて幸せですよね?
Tell me, tell me, you must be happy, right?
もしこのまま消えたら愛されるのなら
If I disappeared now, if I were loved like this
今すぐにでも綺麗に亡くなりたい
I'd die happy now for being beautiful
こんなはずないわよダヴィンチ
Don't paint me like that, DaVinci
もう少しだけべっぴんに
Make me a little prettier
コントラストも入れて頂戴
Add contrast to that too
全世界を懲らしめたい
I want the world to see this
Look at this, uh
Look at this
Look at this 悲しいかも ey, ey, ey
Look at this, it might be sad, ey, ey, ey
もう少し肌に艶を頂戴
Put a little more shine on my skin
女盛り舐めたらヤイ
Hey, don't mess with a woman in her prime
トイレに女神はおったんかい?
Is there a goddess watching you in the bathroom?
おったなら捕まえなさい
If you let it drop, pick it back up
ちゃんみな最近まじかわいい
They say Chanmina is so cute lately
私は忘れないあの嵐
I'll never forget those storms
あの時私はまだセブンティーン
Back then when I was still seventeen
あの時言ったよな
Back then, you said, didn't you?
You can't be beautiful
You can't be famous
醜いブスが歌ってんじゃないよ
Don't sing if you're an ugly bitch
あの時狂った精神に才能が開花
Back then, while my mind was going crazy, my talent bloomed
味わった幸も不幸も一般じゃなかった
All the happiness and unhappiness I've experienced have matured me
本物を君は知ってるかい?
Do you know what's real?
知識と経験のエロス
Eros of knowledge and experience
まだ使いもんになってるかい?
Are you still using that?
女は皆正気じゃない
We women are all insane
(I am beautiful)
Look at this, uh
Look at this
Look at this 悲しいかも ey ey ey
Look at this, it might be sad, ey, ey, ey
もう少し肌に艶を頂戴
Put a little more shine on my skin
女盛り舐めたらヤイ
Hey, don't mess with a woman in her prime
トイレに女神はおったんかい?
Is there a goddess watching you in the bathroom?
おったなら捕まえなさい
If you let it drop, pick it back up
Can you hear me Mina, are you the beauty?
Say July you are the 真 fucking beauty
Say July, you are the true fucking beauty
予想違い驚きなさい
Be surprised, I'm not what you expect
磨いたらダイヤ美しい
Refine me like a beautiful diamond
悲観的いや美学的
Pessimist? No, aesthetic
(前例がないのは怖いかい?)
(Are you afraid because there's no precedent?)
磨いたらダイヤ美しい
Refine me like a beautiful diamond
(ならお手本になりなさい)
(Then become the example)
生きなさい今魅せなさい
Live the charm now
(怖がったままでどうすんだい?)
(Are you feeling a fear that never goes away?)
あなたこそダイヤ美しい
You are a beautiful diamond
(あの彼女を助けなさい)
(Now go and cure that)
I'm a fucking woman
And I'm fucking beautiful
God here I am
We're fucking women
And we're fucking beautiful, yeah
Ah! Look everyone!
I finally have a new outfit!
見て見て見て！新衣装！どう？可愛い？
Look, look, look! New outfit! How is it? Cute?
どう？どう？どう？
How? How? How?
Do I look cute? Oh!
It's performance Bae!
You want to have a close-up?
This thing has so many things I want to show off!
Starting from the top, top-down, from the head...
Look at that hair! Look at that fade!
かっこよくない？
Isn't it cool?
I asked for a wolf cut...
...that's also half-up, half-down, so it's really easy to dance in.
めっちゃ踊りやすくて！
It's so easy to dance in!
可愛いっしょ？まぁ、可愛い、かっこいいっしょ？あははは。
Cute, right? Well, cute and cool, right? Ahahaha.
And then, uh, what else, what else? Oh, my makeup!
メイクも可愛いでしょ？ エヘヘヘ！
My makeup is cute too, right? Hehehe!
And then I have so many, like, hand accessories as well.
Look at that! Look how cool that is!
And then we'll do like a quick scan of the... T-pose quick scan.
Quick scan of the body.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
There's also something very special.
I have an MC tail now.
If you noticed earlier, normally when I dance, I have my tail just, you know, free.
But you know, this is the MC resting tail.
Cause the tail also needs resting periods as well.
So this is my MC tail.
Very cute! I hope you guys like it!
Oh my god! And this was designed by, of course, the amazing Mika-mama!
ありがとうございます！ めっちゃくちゃ可愛いデザインになりました。
Thank you very much! It turned into a very, very cute design.
ありがとうございます！ エヘヘ。
Thank you very much! Hehehe.
But that's not all.
I mean, if I get a new outfit, I feel like it's only fair that...
...some other people get new outfits!
おーい！ 来て来て来て！
Hey! Come here, come here, come here!
Ahhh! The Bae Dancers also get new outfits!
You get an outfit! You get an outfit! Everyone gets an outfit!
Look at them! Oh, oh, oh...
Oh yeah! Oh wow! Oh so sexy! Oh!
So the new dancers have also, of course, upgraded outfits.
They have shorts with the boots, and the socks, and the jacket.
Wow, look at that! Amazing!
And then on the back of the jacket, they have my logo.
後ろにロゴもあります。
There is also a logo on the back.
Whoa! Kawaii!
I also designed... well, not designed, but I wanted the design...
...to be easy for them to dance in as well.
So this is the upgraded Bae Dance Team! Yay!
どう？ 可愛い？
How is it? Cute?
うん。 ポーズ。 ポーズ。
Yeah. Pose. Pose.
可愛い！ イェーイ！
Cute! Yay!
まあ、せっかくなんでね。
Well, since we're here.
Since we all have new outfits, I think it's only fitting that...
...we continue the rest of the live like this, with our new outfits!
じゃ、踊りますか？
Well then, shall we dance?
We're gonna do the next song on the stage over there.
行くぞ！
Let's go!
よいしょ、よいしょ、よいしょ...
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho...
よいしょ、よいしょ。 いや緊張すんな。
Heave-ho, heave-ho. Man, don't be nervous.
はい！ じゃ、どうぞ！
Alright! Now then, here you go!
[Title: キツネノマド (Queen Fox)]
SHOWTIME, WASSA!
月の光を呑む 僕の夜が来た
The night of my moonlight-drinking has come
僕の夜が来た
My night has come
けたたましく現れる ONE, TWO
Appearing noisily, one, two
危険探して KNOCK, KNOCK, KNOCK!
Looking for danger, knock, knock, knock!
Don't mess it up! Forget it, make a finger
窓を見て 行き過ぎ my eyes
Look at the window, you can see my eyes
その瞳に出会ったら
If you meet those eyes,
お前も仲間 Come come, say it!
you're a comrade, come come, say it!
化生のものか 魔性のものか
Are you a spirit of vanity, or a spirit of mischief?
正体現せ ay, ta da da da da
Reveal your true form, ay, ta da da da da
変装体 Love it, 僕見て Know it
Disguised, love it, see me, know it
Lai lai lai lai ya (Come again?)
化け捨て Love it, 存在 Know it
Reveal it, love it, existence, know it
Peek-a-boo (Show me show me eyes)
Don't worry, 傷つけないよ Raiaia
Don't worry, I won't hurt you, raiaia
I let you, このミステリー Ai yai yai yai ya
I let you, in this mystery, ai yai yai yai ya
See this finger trap!
Tomorrow make it rough, today make it fire
目を逸らさないで Make it loud your voice
Don't avert your eyes, make it loud your voice
よっしゃ、よっしゃ、よっそそれ！ お狐様に任せよう！
Good, good, stop it, fear, leave it to the Fox Spirit!
光を騙して作るんだ Night
Making a night by deceiving the light
あちこち目覚めて闇が喝采
Awakening here and there, the darkness is applause
Hey, ほらこっちおいで
Hey, look, come here
Yeah, just shout out the spell!
化生のものか 魔性のものか (Tick-tock-tick-tock)
Are you a spirit of vanity, or a spirit of mischief? (tick-tock-tick-tock)
正体現せ ay, ta da da da da
Reveal your true form, ay, ta da da da da
見たい体 Love it, 僕は Know it
Untried, love it, I know it
Lai lai lai lai ya (Come again?)
この世界変えねしみしたい期待して
Change this world, see me, expect it
Peek-a-boo (Show me show me eyes)
Don't worry, 傷つけないよ Raiaia
Don't worry, I won't hurt you, raiaia
I let you, さあ百鬼夜行へ Ai yai yai yai ya
I let you, now, to the myriad demons, ai yai yai yai ya
Hey, follow the Queen Fox
I'm the real master of this night
Hey, follow your Queen Fox
見せられて Dan dan dan
Enchanted, enchanted, dan dan dan
重なり合った (World), 僕たちのショウウィンドウ
Overlapping (world), our show window
射抜くような眼差し、君に届いている？
Does this insightful gaze reach you?
Why don't you know? It's time now
どんな姿でも構わない世界へ
To a world that doesn't care what form you take
化生のものか 魔性のものか 正体現せ
Are you a spirit of vanity, or a spirit of mischief? Reveal your true form
正体現せ
Reveal your true form
変装体 Love it, 僕見て Know it
Disguised, love it, see me, know it
【キツネノマド (Queen Fox)】
[Title: Queen Fox]
Yeah!
変身してラバー 僕を見ておくれ ライライライライヤ
Transform and be my lover, look at me
Lai lai lai lai ya
朱色、青、ラバー 存在の上 ナイナイナイナイヤ
Vermilion, blue, lover, above existence
Nai nai nai nai ya
Don't worry 傷つけないよ ライライライライヤ
Don't worry, I won't hurt you
Lai lai lai lai ya
あっち、こっち、ミステリー アイアイアイアイヤ
Here, there, mystery
Ai ai ai ai ya
あっち、そっち、身も闇 アイアイアイアイヤ
Here, there, body and darkness
Ai ai ai ai ya
This finger trap!
Just shout out the spell!
Yeah! Be the Queen Fox!
【威風堂々】
Lyrics, Music: 梅とら
[Title: Ifuudoudou]
[Lyrics, Music: Umetora]
時に噛んだりして 痛みを覚えさせて
Sometimes biting,
making you remember the pain.
溢れる液体で汚してよ 全部
Dirty me with overflowing liquid, all of it.
足の先からずっと 馳せせたその神経はもう
All the way from the tips of my toes,
those nerves I've quickened are already...
感触に溺れる身体 心を連れて
...my body drowning in the sensation,
taking my heart with it.
Oh, oh, 指くわえた我慢の中
Oh, oh, amidst the finger-sucking endurance
Oh, oh, 欲して逃がしそう
Oh, oh, wanting it, almost letting it escape.
いらない 全てはいらない
磨き上げてる 邪魔なプライド
No need, I don't need anything,
this polished, bothersome pride.
意味ない 世界のルール
くらいだとしか言いようがない
Meaningless world rules,
I can only say they're dark.
隠しているあなたのスタイル
剥き出しにあるがままのダイス
Your hidden style,
the dice exposed as they are.
そこに生まれるのは 期待外れなんかじゃない
叩きのめすマインド
What's born there isn't some disappointment,
it's a mind to beat down.
吐息合わせた相性 耳に吹きかける感情
Compatibility with matched breaths,
emotions blown into ears.
破裂しそうな胸 騒ぎ出すサイン
A chest about to burst, a sign that starts to stir.
脱ぎかけてるシャツ 優しく裂いてよまず
A shirt halfway off,
first, gently tear it.
かまわず Get blind もがいたまらないで
Don't mind, get blind, don't stop struggling.
Ah, ah, 自由な世界のど真ん中
Ah, ah, right in the middle of a free world
Ah, ah, 夢見てるのさ本性を
Ah, ah, I'm dreaming of my true nature
いらない 全てはいらない
怖じ気づいた野望のトライ
No need, I don't need anything,
the trial of a cowed ambition.
満足なんてそこにない 目に見える哀れな未来
There's no satisfaction there,
the pitiful future you can see.
思い通りにできるライフ 手にできるわ あなた次第
A life you can live as you wish,
you can have it, it's up to you.
隠したりなんかはしない
誰よりも誇らしげにできるマインド
I won't hide anything,
a mind that can be prouder than anyone else's.
ほらこの世界の中 他にはない
Look, in this world,
there's nothing else.
確かなもの 自分以外は
Anything certain, other than myself.
Shut up and keep time, I got no time, alright?
Don't get twitchy, go edgy, 全開で行っちゃ Burn, burn, burn!
Don't get twitchy, go edgy,
go at full throttle, burn, burn, burn!
欲しがってるのは 気持ちいいの もっと
What you're wanting is to feel good, more.
あるがままの想い 入れちゃって なりで Get
Put in your feelings as they are,
get it as it goes.
ほらこの世界で今 解き放って
Look, in this world now, release it.
鋭くギラつかせて 希望
Make it sharp and glaring, hope.
もっと本気出していいよ
You can be more serious.
OW!
【HIT ME UP】
Lyrics: KIRA, monii, Johnny R
[Title: HIT ME UP]
[Lyrics: KIRA, monii, Johnny R]
Huh! Come chase me
Everyday I spent crying 'bout almost-loves turned complicated
Everyday I spent crying 'bout
almost-loves turned complicated
On the way yah my heart got torn up, shredded, all but dead and
On the way yah my heart got torn up,
shredded, all but dead and
Now they say I, I'm just a masochist, they're sick of it
Now they say I, I'm just a masochist,
they're sick of it
Boy take a hint, you ain't gon' ever get this
Boy take a hint,
you ain't gon' ever get this
Pedal to the metal, shootin' straight to the stars
Pedal to the metal,
shootin' straight to the stars
Got a cravin', like the danger on me
(Yeah she like it like that, like that)
Up another level, temptation you just can't deny
Up another level,
temptation you just can't deny
Come get a taste but can't say I won't bite
Come get a taste
but can't say I won't bite
Supersonic, I'm heading out, I'm gonna... (Ahh)
...in my eyes, nirvana
(Oh I'm taking off now!)
Pushing for the high, my lover, I gotta (Run)
But it's fun to see you try
(So hit me up!)
Off the map I'mma take it, all my energy
Speedin' up fast
Ready, target locked
(So hit me up!)
Hit the dash, I'm upgraded and you want a piece
So hit me up, ah
I never stop
In a new territory
I'm on the edge of glory
(Boy just watch how I move)
Gimme that rush
Got no regrets in my mind
Boy, it's on you this time
So hit me up
Outta luck, volume up
You got a crush?
Such a cliché, your bad boy charms
Thought I'd fall right back in your arms
Wasn't enough, you needed more
Now you're begging to let you score
Surely you'll take it all in stride
I'mma be busy tonight
Goodbye, goodbye
Gotta leave you dry
Always try'na play it cool
20/20 vision on me
Just outside my field of view
(Yeah she like it like that, like that)
Engine booming, that's my cue
Catch me if you can, you better
Keep up the chase, boy you're falling behind
Supersonic, I'm heading out, I'm gonna (Ahh)
In my eyes, nirvana (Oh I'm taking off now!)
Pushing for the high, my lover, I gotta (Run)
But it's fun to see you try
(So hit me up!)
Off the map I'mma take it, all my energy
Speedin' up fast
Ready, target locked
(So hit me up!)
Hit the dash, I'm upgraded and you want a piece
So hit me up, ah
I never stop
In a new territory
I'm on the edge of glory
(Boy just watch how I move)
Gimme that rush
Got no regrets in my mind
Boy, it's on you this time
So hit me up
Outta luck, volume up
You got a crush?
Just barely wasn't enough, you shoulda...
Just barely wasn't enough, you should've...
If you put me over the top, you coulda...
If you put me over the top, you could've...
Coming full circle, I hit enough
Top spot getting hot, watch me run it up
(So hit me up!)
Revving up and make that vroom vroom vroom vroom
When I hit you with that zoom zoom zoom zoom
If you know what's good for you you you you
Now I'm back in charge, ride that underdog!
YEAH!
I hope you enjoyed that!
Did you guys enjoy? Did you guys enjoy?
We had a couple of songs with a couple of important people,
which I want to call in to help with this next MC part.
Special guests! Special guests!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
みんなさん！ Yeah!
Everyone! Yeah!
What's up!
Introduce yourselves, please! Please, go ahead.
ホロライブEnglish CHAD CASTの森カリオペです！
I'm Mori Calliope from Hololive English's CHAD CAST!
What's up desu desu! Hey guys, hope you enjoyed our performances!
Hi-RyS, it's IRyS also from CHAD CAST!
Let's go! Yeah! Chad!
Here to rumble!
Yeah! What's this movement?
Rumble? Did you say name?
Rumble? Did you say your name?
I said rumble!
Oh! I'm pretty sure she said IRyS.
I'm pretty sure she said IRyS.
Wait, my brain's not working... it's a big day, guys...
...it's a big day, guys, because she's dancing!
Guys!
Oh yeah, I mean, yeah obviously yeah woah!
What are you doing? It's so cool! It's so cool!
It looks... dynamic.
You look like a K-pop star!
Oh yeah! I'm so glad you like it!
And look, the MC tail is back.
I've got to put it to rest for a little bit, after all that dancing.
So special.
But we performed some songs together.
Um, first we had... If...
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Yeah! Yeah, we know! Awesome!
It's awesome, it's great!
It was a sexy song.
How do you feel about that song? Thank you so much.
How do I feel? Yeah.
How do you feel about that song?
Feelings, thoughts, opinions?
I feel great about it!
I think it was an amazing... embraced herself...
Hit... so hit me up! Hit me up!
It's so cool! I'm so happy.
We practiced so hard! Yeah we did!
It was fun practicing together though.
Three of us, two of us at a time. It's always fun. Goodbye!
I'm so happy I'm able to dance for you guys on my birthday! Yay!
Not birthday. Birthday, but not birthday. On birthday?
Unbirthday. Unbirthday. She's being unbirthed.
What?! That sounds so wrong!
Save it for the chat, guys. IRyS, save it for the chat.
But after dancing, I am feeling a little bit, you know... hot!
Hot! She's getting hot in here!
Is she gonna take off all her clothes?
Whoa! IRyS, stay in your stream! Maybe not!
I'll be right back! Oh, what is she taking off?
She's gonna take off her pants!
Why would she take off her pants, IRyS? What is she thinking about? Oh my god!
Alright, you know what? No! Stop! You need to be stopped!
Akeru zo... oh, she coming in! Oh, oh!
I'm gonna open it... oh, she's coming in! Oh, oh!
Whoa! Behold!
I took off my jacket! Oh my god!
She looks so fancy here! You can see all her...
Yeah, you can see all my accessories now!
カッコいい！ I love the spikes! Yeah!
Cool! I love the spikes! Yeah!
It's like a wristband, but I have an arm cuff now as well.
Eh, cool!
Now I can dance even more with no restrictions!
She's even more dynamic! My god, more dynamic!
Yes, no pigtails to get in the way either, like...
Oh my god, she's popping off! All the arms!
ま、せっかくなのでね。 Since we're all here together...
Well, since we're here. Since we're all here together...
How would you guys feel about maybe doing one more song together?
Okay! I don't have the energy, but I'll do my best!
頑張れ、頑張れ、頑張れ！ Yeah! You can do it!
Do your best, do your best, do your best! Yeah! You can do it!
That being said, I hope you guys are ready as well.
We're gonna bring you one more CHAD CAST performance! Let's go!
Ready, set, let's go!
あじまうあじまうあじまーう！！！
Ajimau ajimau ajimau!!!
宿題が全ッッ然終わらない、全国のヤバめな諸君！
Homework isn't finished at all, to all the danger-zone students across the nation!
時間がなければ、眠らなきゃ良いじゃない
If you have no time, why not just not sleep?
がんばれ、がんばれ、あたし…
Do your best, do your best, me...
パーリラ　脳内フロア
Party Night, inside my brain's floor
暴れてる　カルナバル
It's raging, a carnival
アドレナリン　ドバドバ
Adrenaline pouring out
究極の　PANIGHT
Ultimate PANIGHT
パリナイ！パリナイ！パーラパッパ　パリナイ！
Party Night! Party Night! Pa-pa-pappa Party Night!
パリナイ！パリナイ！おわるくナイ？
Party Night! Party Night! Isn't it okay to not end?
We Are ＼NEGI☆U／
We Are NEGI☆U
Let’s Go!!
Let's Go!!
スゴい　ヤバい　パない　物足りない
Amazing, dangerous, outrageous, not enough
ないない尽くしでとめとない
Running out of everything, it never ends
スゴい　ヤバい　パない　Saturday Night
Amazing, dangerous, outrageous, Saturday Night
とにかくもう　やるしかない
Anyway, I have to do it
どすこい
Dosukoi!
ヤバい　パない　物足りない
Dangerous, outrageous, not enough
全力モノモノ申したい
I want to make a complaint with all my might
たった一度の青春は
This only-once youth
毎日ENJOY！Party Night
ENJOY everyday! Party Night
あーお集まりの旦那様、えー、そうじゃない様、ご唱和ください
Ah, gathered gentlemen, eh, people who aren't, please chant along
それゆけ Say
Here we go, Say
Wow ＼Wow／ Wow ＼Wow／ Wow ＼Wow／
Wow (Wow) Wow (Wow) Wow (Wow)
ddd DJ!!
PA PA PA PA…
PA PA PA PA...
PANIGHT!!
Everybody Sing Along
でっち上げ　進化論
Fabricated theory of evolution
陽キャでも陰キャでも
Whether you're a sunny person or a gloomy person
勉強だ Wassup!! Wassup!!
Study, Wassup!! Wassup!!
太陽は銀河系？
The sun is in the galaxy?
おしゃぺり　ノンノンノン！
Chatting, no-no-no!
遊んじゃダメダメ
Playing is not allowed
ごめんなさーい！
I'm so sorry!
朝が来て　眠れない　どうしよう…
Morning comes, can't sleep, what should I do...
神様も　両手挙げて　Fly High
Even God gives up and raises both hands, Fly High
なんとか　するしかない
I just have to do something about it
頑張れ　出来るって
Do your best, you can do it
ド派手にカマしちゃる
I'll do it flashily
ネバギバ　Put your Hands up
Never give up, Put your Hands up
タリナイ！タリナイ！ターラタッタ　タリナイ！
Not enough! Not enough! Ta-ra-tatta Not enough!
タリナイ！タリナイ！時間がない
Not enough! Not enough! There's no time
We Are ＼NEGI☆U／
We Are NEGI☆U
Let’s Go!!
Let's Go!!
スゴい　ヤバい　パない　物足りない
Amazing, dangerous, outrageous, not enough
体裁のパッチワーク　勝てやしない
The scale's a mess, it doesn't even have a shape
スゴい　ヤバい　パない　Sunday Night
Amazing, dangerous, outrageous, Sunday Night
とにかくもう　やるしかない
Anyway, I have to do it
どすこい　ヤバい　パない　物足りない
Dosukoi! Dangerous, outrageous, not enough
宿題やっぱり終わらない
Homework really isn't finished!
たった一度の青春は
This only-once youth
脳内ハッピー　Party Night
Inside my brain, a happy Party Night
この問題全然わかんないんですけど！
This problem, I don't understand it at all!
ベアちゃんの新衣装めっちゃ可愛いじゃん！
Bae, your new outfit is so cute!
でしょ？キラキラ光るんですよ！
Right? It shines glittery!
へー、みんな元気だな。
Heh, everyone's so energetic.
火を被ってこんな時も、すごいな。
Enjoying themselves even at a time like this, amazing.
Yeah, yeah, Party Party! Whoo!
※お書きになったそんな音楽は現在使われておりません。
*The music you've written is no longer in use.
もう一度お書き直しください
Please rewrite it once more.
意味わかんねぇ!
I don't get it!
サイバーパンクデッドボーイ
[Song: Cyberpunk Deadboy]
どーせ誰も聴いてなんかいないさ
No one's listening anyway,
音楽なんて全部ファッション
music is all just fashion.
音亡喰らって選手退場
Killed by the sound, player out,
ワンナイ
one night.
どーせ何も伝えてなんかないさ
Nothing's being conveyed anyway,
なんとかトック撮って売名
recording some Tok for fame,
あんな気取っておいて最低
acting so pretentious, it's the worst.
グンナイ
Good night.
どうしたってどう見たって
No matter what, no matter how you look at it,
尊師達でもう大渋滞
the gurus are causing a major traffic jam.
それでもあっち、こっち、そっち、ぼっち、卍、Zエイジ
Still, here, there, everywhere, lonely, Gen Z.
猿も欲しがるパンチライン欲しいの
I want the punchlines even monkeys crave.
意味とかどっちだっていいよ
Meaning doesn't really matter.
歌詞とかどうでも良いのでノれるの下さい
Lyrics don't matter either, just give me a beat.
さあ皆で笑いましょう
Now then, let's all laugh.
芸術より数の大小？
Size over artistry?
ヴァイラスに酷い代償
A heavy price for the virus.
じゃあどうすんの？それでいいんだっけ？
Then what? Is that really okay?
頭は空回りタヒんでいく
My mind's spinning, fading away.
ふざけるな バイバイバズメロディ
Don't screw with me, bye-bye buzz melody.
疑えよ大概嘘ばかり
Doubt it all, most of it is just lies.
化けんな 幻想でも理想でも良い
Don't transform; fantasy or ideal, it's fine.
君の歌いたかった物はどうしたんだい？
What happened to what you wanted to sing?
ぶざまでも オーライ 嘘じゃない
Pathetic is alright, it's not a lie.
お金や擬奏で満たす前に
Before filling it with money or fake play,
負けんな覚醒せよ鼓動達よ
don't lose; awaken, my heartbeats.
君の伝えたかった物はどうしたんだい？
What happened to what you wanted to convey?
意味わかんねぇ!
I don't get it!
※お書きになったそんな音楽は現在使われておりません。
*The music you've written is no longer in use.
ポップソング、ヒットソング聴いてもう一度お書き直しください
Listen to pop hits and rewrite it again.
あーもうハイカラ作家ばっか洒落くさいわ
Ah, these trendy writers are so pretentious.
はぁ…
(Sigh...)
どいつもこいつもそいつもあいつも意味わかんねぇ!
Every single one of them, I don't get it!
どうしたってどうみたって
No matter what, no matter how you look at it,
尊師達でもう大渋滞
the gurus are causing a major traffic jam.
それでもあっち、こっち、そっち、ぼっち、卍、Zエイジ
Still, here, there, everywhere, Gen Z.
猿も欲しがるパンチライン欲しいの
I want the punchlines even monkeys crave.
意味とかどっちだっていいよ
Meaning doesn't really matter.
歌詞とかどうでもいいので伸びるの下さい
Lyrics don't matter; give me something viral.
さあ皆で祓いましょう
Now then, let's all exorcise it.
芸術より数なんでしょう？
It's about the numbers rather than art, right?
ヴァイラスに酷い代償
A heavy price for the virus.
じゃあどうすんの？それでいいんだっけ？
Then what? Is that really okay?
頭は空回りタヒんでいく
My mind's spinning, fading away.
ふざけるな バイバイバズメロディ
Don't screw with me, bye-bye buzz melody.
疑えよ大概嘘ばかり
Doubt it all, most of it is just lies.
化けんな 幻想でも理想でも良い
Don't transform; fantasy or ideal, it's fine.
君の歌いたかった物はどうしたんだい？
What happened to what you wanted to sing?
このままじゃ到底終われない
I can't possibly end it like this.
欲しいのはきっとお金じゃない
What I want is surely not money.
負けんな 覚醒せよ 鼓動達よ
Don't lose; awaken, my heartbeats.
君の歌いたかった物がきっとあるんだ
There must be something you wanted to sing.
ふざけるな… ふざけるな!
Don't screw with me... Don't screw with me!
バイバイバズメロディ
Bye-bye buzz melody.
疑えよ大概嘘ばかり
Doubt it all, most of it is just lies.
化けんな 幻想でも理想でも良い
Don't transform; fantasy or ideal, it's fine.
君の歌いたかった物はどうしたんだい？
What happened to what you wanted to sing?
ぶざまでもオーライ 嘘じゃない
Pathetic is alright, it's not a lie.
お金や擬奏で満たす前に
Before filling it with money or fake play,
負けんな覚醒せよ 鼓動達よ
don't lose; awaken, my heartbeats.
僕の伝えたかった物はどうしたんだい？
What happened to what I wanted to convey?
意味わかんねぇ!
I don't get it!
意味わかんねぇよ!
I don't get it at all!
意味わかんねぇ!
I don't get it!
V
[Song: V]
バ・チャ・ラ・ラ・ラ・ラ・ラ・ラ
Ba-cha-la-la-la-la-la-la
I'm a V
バ・チャ・ラ・ラ・ラ・ラ・ラ・ラ
Ba-cha-la-la-la-la-la-la
I'm a V
バ・チャ・ラ・ラ・ラ・ラ・ラ・ラ
Ba-cha-la-la-la-la-la-la
I'm a V, I'm a V, I'm a V, I'm a V
たかだか生身の混濁
Just a chaos of flesh and blood,
触らば可愛いの魂胆
if you touch it, it's a cute scheme.
たくま。はなから。ほら。
Strong. From the start. See.
落としてあげる
I'll let it fall.
はい。聡明。払。デモン。キュートなら免。嫌。
Yes. Clear. Exorcise. Demon. If it's cute, exempt. Hate.
解。腹立た。レッテル。いってる。メンタルは...
Liberation. Pissed off. Label. Going crazy. My mental is...
あぁ...
Ah...
最強スマイルで
With the strongest smile,
転がして。ファントム。
spinning it. Phantom.
誤魔化したり。昇進。証。去。去。去。バイバイ。
Deceiving. Promotion. Proof. Leave. Leave. Leave. Bye bye.
にゃんでな
Why though?
I am a V, I am a V, I am a V, Our, Our, Yo
I am a V, Jana, Diva, Midara wa yo, Yo
I am a V, Jena, Diva, Obsessed with you, Yo
夢見てる少年。夢見てる少女。
Dreaming boys. Dreaming girls.
V なら V だわ。余。余。余。余。
If it's a V, then it's a V. I. I. I. I.
No! ちょんぎり。ガリガリ。モンスター。
No! Cut it off. Scratching. Monster.
我ら。せな。我。センター。
Us. Now. I'm center.
誰よりも客寄せ。パンダ。
Drawing more crowds than anyone. Panda.
我は何だ？まるで生んだ？
What am I? As if I was born?
自己愛制。勝。証。
Self-love system. Win. Proof.
M-I-V, M-I-C, A-I-Z-A-I, M-I-C, S-A-R-A-I-N-I, W-Y-N-I
Oh my name is V, V, V...
Oh my name is V, V, V, V...
めでたられたら箱までラブだ
If I'm celebrated, I'll love you to the box
I'm a V, V, V...
アン・ドゥ・トロワでまた箱までラブだ
Un, deux, trois, and love you to the box again
I'm a V-DA!
I'm a V!
心の中スムーズ like a butter
Inside my heart, smooth like butter
タッチしたいならほれエンド・エンド
If you want to touch, here, end to end
キャッチ・ミー・ザ・ハイピース
Catch me, the high piece
召し上がれ我が分はわからんない
Help yourself, I don't even know my own share
我心叫ぶ一つのライヴ
My heart screams, a single live
生きる姿や魂を今
My living form and soul, right now
二つにして愛をバラバラに
Divide them in two, scattering love
生まれた時の喜びはモーション
The joy of being born is motion
さよならで今 駄目ね
With a goodbye, right now, it's no good
I am a V, I am a V, I am a awa-awa-ya
I am the V, the Diva, the midara-wa-ya
夢見てる少年 夢見てる少女で
Dreaming boy, dreaming girl
VならVだわ あま・あま・あま・あま
If it's a V, it's a V, ama-ama-ama-ama
NO!
強要さ 子供の頃 言われたもんだ
Coercion, that's what I was told as a child
あのヒーロー 少女の人形の背中には
On the back of that hero, that girl's doll
翼ついてないから 儚いな
There are no wings, so it's fleeting
ワッチャ・ザ・ヒューマンだ 死のこの優雅
Watcha the human, the elegance of this death
存在はワン・ワン・だ 吠えても 惚れても
Existence is wan-wan, even if you bark or fall in love
死ぬのはバラバラだ！
Dying is all scattered!
惚れたら死ぬぞ
If you fall for me, you'll die
I'm a V.
助けて！めっちゃ疲れた！ I'm so tired!
Help! I'm so tired! I'm so tired!
I hope you guys have been enjoying the show.
We had so many bangers after bangers after bangers.
A lot of dancing. We had Power Night, we had Cyberpunk, Deep Boy...
...we had V.
My arms are dead, everything dead.
But! That's not the end of the show yet.
We gotta keep going on and on and on and on and on!
And here I bring you a very, very, very important and exciting announcement.
I am about to perform a song that no one has heard before.
No one! Except for me. Because it's my new song!
I've been hyping this up for a while now because I'm really, really excited...
...and this will be the first time that I'm sharing it with all of you.
So I hope you enjoy. More information after I perform it...
...'cause you gotta see it first, you know? Wish me luck!
I'm nervous, but we got this! ここからは... 何と新曲です！
I'm nervous, but we got this! And now... a new song!
めちゃくちゃ緊張するんだけど、頑張ってパフォーマンスしたいと思います。
I'm super nervous, but I'll do my best to perform for you.
どうぞ！
Please enjoy!
준비～!
Ready!
That's Good Game, What a shame.
Players, they all complain
"Why me?" "No not again!"
Shout! Ratatata～
But! Ain't got time so dry those eyes
Look around what's that I spy
The Broken and Bruised
All got something to prove now
Abracadabra let's go
Watch them like dice as they fall (they fall)
끝까지 가보자 Go
Let's go to the end, Go
나는 내 맘 대로해, Hey
I'll do as I like, Hey
Double one, Double win
Lowly to Lottery Do or Die
We hit that high (Snake eyes, snake eyes)
Come on now don't be shy (Snake eyes, snake eyes)
뜨겁게 달아올라 (불타올라)
It's heating up (Burning up)
놀자 all day all night (all day all night)
Let's play all day all night (all day all night)
So turn it up can't stop won't stop preachin
Who said the sky's the limit?
Show them that we mean business
We are the young and vicious
Snake eyes they never lie
Fly high with pride and leave your fears behind
지겨워! 우리들의 광란의 Party
I'm sick of it! Our crazy Party
보여줄게 환상 Safari
I'll show you a fantasy Safari
baddie baddie, nobody can stop me
끼리끼리 붙어, Come on closer!
Birds of a feather, Come on closer!
Go! Go! 더 빨리 (Check It Out)
Go! Go! Faster (Check It Out)
Actin all Naughty
싹다 부셔 모조리 모조리
Break it all, every last bit
싹다다다다!
Everything!
Shake it off, what goes around
Shut your mouth, will come back down
Ready the fight, Ready the screaming
Abracadabra let's go
Watch it we reapin it all (reapin it all)
Watch it we're reaping it all (reaping it all)
꺾이지 않는 의지
An unbreakable will,
될 대로 돼볼래 Play
letting it be what it will be, Play.
Reason, Our demon
Believe in the beaten
Just wait and see
We hit that high
Snake eyes, Snake eyes
Come on now don't be shy
뜨겁게 달아올라 (불타올라)
Heating up (Burning up)
놀자 all day all night (all day all night)
Let's play all day all night (all day all night)
Let the beat drop!
GO!
We Go hard (Go hard)
기사회생 전부를 걸어 Bet
Back from the dead, bet it all
GO!
We Go hard
I want it all
다시 일어나 파괴와 재생
Rising again, destruction and rebirth
죽지 않아, 전부 걸어
I won't die, bet it all
맞서 싸워, 시작이야
Fight back, this is the beginning
Take the crown
끝까지 달려가
Running until the end,
Rule the game
We'll hit that high
Snake eyes, Snake eyes
Come on now don't be shy
같이 춤을 춰봐, 이렇게
Dance with me, just like this
멈출 순 없어
I can't stop now,
같이 Dance all night
let's dance all night together!
Don't be afraid of losing
It's just a new beginning
Look at the cards we dealing
Look at the cards we're dealing
Sometimes it takes a villain
Snake eyes the time is nigh
Fly high with pride and leave all fears behind!
It's finally out!
I hope you all enjoyed my new song, Snake Eyes!
This has been such a long process in the making...
I can't even talk, I'm exhausted, but also I'm so happy it's finally out.
My newest song, Snake Eyes, was what I just performed.
Not only is it the first time that I've written a lot of the lyrics from scratch for, you know...
Not only is it the first time that I've written a lot of the lyrics from scratch,
But also it's the first time choreographing a multi-member song with, you know, the two back dancers.
but also the first time choreographing a multi-member song with the two backup dancers.
I'm so happy! I did it!
I hope you guys enjoyed it.
Now, very important, pay attention.
The MV of this new song is also going to be premiering very soon after the live is over.
And it is going to be my first ever 3D music video!
やっとね、新曲がちょっとね、あの、公開した、ので、
Finally, my new song has been released,
めちゃくちゃ嬉しいです。
so I'm incredibly happy.
このあと、ライブの後ね、あの、初の3D MVもプレミアするので、
After this live, my first 3D MV will premiere,
見てください！お願いします！
so please watch it! I'm counting on you!
歌詞、え、英語の歌詞はほぼ、あの、自分で書いたので、
The lyrics—I wrote most of the English lyrics myself,
あと韓国語もね、あの、頑張ってたんで、あの、聞いてください！
and I worked hard on the Korean part too, so please listen to it!
Streaming should also begin shortly after as well.
It should be local time midnight. I never know anything, but it'll happen soon.
So please make sure to check it out afterwards.
I hope I did okay. I don't know, I was stressed about the choreography for a very long time, but...
I hope I did okay. I was stressed about the choreography for a very long time, but...
Now is the time!
It's the thing you've all been waiting for!
A merch showcase!
グッズ紹介に入りたいと思います！
I'd like to get into the merchandise showcase!
This is the lineup for this time!
Baelz Hakos 2026 Birthday Live!
Birthday Merch! This is what the full set looks like.
Birthday merch is what the full set looks like.
フルセットはこんな感じです！
This is what the full set looks like!
Let's look at them one by one.
What do we have first? First up...
We have the [ReCOLOR] Rubber Mat!
Look at that beauty!
This illustration is of course by my beloved mama, Mika Pikazo sensei.
This illustration is of course by my beloved mama, Mika Pikazo-sensei.
今年もね、書いてくださってありがとうございます。
Thank you for drawing it again this year.
I just thought, you know, my very first birthday merch also actually had a rubber mat in it.
And since, you know, I have a new outfit, I thought it was only fitting that we have another rubber mat...
And since I have a new outfit, I thought it was only fitting that we have another rubber mat
...for me to switch out.
I really want this, so that's why I made it.
And you know, you can use it for Holocard...
[ReCOLOR] Rubber Mat
[Title: [ReCOLOR] Rubber Mat]
Also look at it on your desk,
and it's just really pretty, look at it.
Ah, look at it!
It's so pretty, it's so pretty.
Thank you so much.
あの、ママ、今年もね、
And also, Mama, this year too,
Mikaママにあのイラスト書いてくださったので、
Mika Mama drew the illustration for me,
あざます！
so thanks!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ぜひぜひ買ってください！
Please, please buy it!
Uh, what's the next item?
Second is...
[ReCOLOR] Plushie Keychain
[Title: [ReCOLOR] Plushie Keychain]
Tada!
The ReCOLOR Plushie Keychain,
designed after my new outfit!
I've always wanted like a mini, you know,
plushie that I came out with.
Um, you know, I have some,
but I think it was just really fitting
because I have a new outfit,
and I wanted a plushie in the new outfit.
I can take her around places, you know,
and you know, you can photograph her,
chuck her, I don't know,
pat her, I don't know, whatever you want to do.
But it's a plushie keychain,
so it comes with a ball chain,
so you can attach it to your bag!
Isn't she so cute?
Look at those squishy cheeks!
めっちゃ可愛いでしょ！
Isn't she super cute!
き、あの、ぬいぐるみキーホルダーなんで、
Since it's a plushie keychain,
なんか、カバンに付けたりとかね、
you can attach it to your bag and stuff,
できるので、
which you can do,
めちゃくちゃ可愛い感じになりました！
so it turned out really cute!
あざます！
Thanks!
えっ、次。
Um, next.
What is the next one?
Lil Plushie Shed (Pouch)
[Title: Lil Plushie Shed (Pouch)]
これです！
This is it!
The Lil Plushie Shed (Pouch).
It is a pouch.
It is a pouch for the plushie.
If you get both, it's like a set, you know,
because you want to take your little Bae
out into the world.
But what if she gets dirty, you know?
Or like, you don't want her to get to...
Or like, you don't want her to get...
you know, if she gets snagged on a corner,
she rips.
You gotta protect your little Bae!
So you have a Lil Plushie Shed
to house your little Bae!
Um, but it fits perfectly,
and you know, you can use it,
the design is also really cool as well.
Next, last but not least,
is something very special.
ASMR Voice Pack "Forever Your Bae"
[Title: ASMR Voice Pack "Forever Your Bae"]
It is a voice pack.
But it is my first ever ASMR voice pack!
I get really embarrassed doing ASMR stuff,
but I just thought, you know,
since it's a special occasion,
maybe it'd be nice to have
my very first ASMR voice pack.
It features an intimate scene
with you guys after the live show.
So if you want to check it out,
please do.
僕、初、初のASMRボイス、
It's my first, first ASMR voice,
シナリオボイスなんで、
scenario voice,
もし、気になってる方はぜひ聞いてください！
so if you're interested, please listen to it!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
It's called "Forever Your Bae".
恥ずかしい...
How embarrassing...
Anyway, here are the set bonuses!
Set Purchase Bonus
[Title: Set Purchase Bonus]
Tada!
The postcard!
You get a limited edition which...
the limited edition, sorry, features
a hand-signed autograph
and also a hand-written message
from yours truly.
Just an extra way to say thank you very much.
Um, and the standard version comes with
the foil-stamped duplicate autograph and message.
Arms about to... about to die,
but it's alright!
Thank you so much.
えっと、特、特典はやばい、
Um, the bonuses, oh no,
読め、漢字がなんだっけ、あの、
I can't read it, what was the kanji...
特典はこちらです！
Here are the bonuses!
あざます！
Thanks!
ポストカード、えっと、あの、
Postcard, um, well,
直筆サインとメッセージがあります。
there's a hand-signed autograph and message.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
Oh my god, my brain is just... it's gone.
I'm so tired, but anyway...
Um, I think that's it!
Oh wait, no!
There's also a bonus voice!
Wait, I forgot!
Um, so with the full set,
there is a bonus voice pack
that is also ASMR,
that's on top of the already ASMR voice pack.
Just a little extra thing to say thank you.
Um, that's it.
I'm embarrassed. Anyway, yes.
それだけです！あざます！はい！
That's all! Thanks! Yes!
Um, yes.
Before we continue, I guess...
um, there is a little bit after,
so I'm gonna go put my jacket on
real quick, if that's okay.
I'll be right back.
ちょっと着替えてきます。
I'm gonna go change real quick.
戻ってきました！
I'm back!
はい！ただいまです！
Yes! I'm back!
えっと、just put on my jacket.
Um, just put on my jacket.
I'm so happy that, you know,
I got to do another birthday live this year,
even though it's not really my birthday.
I'm so happy that I got to show my new outfit.
I'm just happy that I got a new outfit.
It's so easy to dance in,
I love the way it looks.
And today I got to dance with so many
of my friends!
It was so much fun!
I got to challenge myself.
It's always an amazing, amazing experience
being able to do a birthday live.
いや、今日ね、あの、
Well today,
いっぱいメンバーと一緒に踊って
I danced with many members
めちゃくちゃ嬉しくて、
and I'm super happy,
もう新衣装もめちゃくちゃ嬉しくて、
and I'm super happy about the new outfit,
もうとにかく嬉しいです！
anyway I'm just happy!
あの、みんなもね、
Um, everyone too...
There's a lot of planning that goes into these,
um, all the staff and everyone,
スタッフさんのみんなもね...
all the staff members too...
Everyone's...
Everyoneの力が必要...
I need everyone's strength...
もうなんだかもう英語か日本語かもう分かんないっすね
Man, I don't even know if I'm speaking English or Japanese anymore.
すいません、はい。
Sorry about that.
I'm just mixing up my languages,
but um please do check out the new song MV
that's coming out shortly.
I'm really, really proud of it.
But that's kind of it. That's all I have for today.
BUT there is a final encore song that I wanted to sing
that I think really sums up today's live.
So if you would like to stay... please stay to the end.
Please listen, please don't go anywhere.
ちょっとこの後最後の一曲あります。
There's one final song coming up after this.
今日のテーマにぴったりの曲だと思ってますので
I think it's the perfect song for today's theme,
最後まで聴いてください。
so please listen until the very end.
はい！
Yes!
あとMV、あの、新曲のMVも見てくださいね。
Also the MV, please check out the new song's MV too.
はい、はい。じゃ、最後の曲、ラスト曲、どうぞ。
Alright. Now, here is the final song. Please enjoy.
魂の色は 何色ですか
The color of the soul, what color is it?
ANIMA / 毛蟹 (LIVE LAB.)
[Song: ANIMA / Lyrics & Music: Kegani (LIVE LAB.)]
Thank you for coming to my live today!
I hope I brought some color to your day!
最後まで盛り上がっていこうぜ！
Let's keep the energy up until the end!
“もういっそ 折れたままで”
"Better just let it remain broken"
捨てるほど 逃げ出すほど強くないよ ほら
To throw it away, runaway, I'm not that strong, see
もう一度 鼓動、高鳴る
Once again my heart beats faster
何が正しいかなんてわからないけど
What’s right I don’t know, but...
形のないものばかりが大切になって行く
It’s the things that have no shape that become precious
飾らない言葉だけが強く結ばれてる
Just unadorned words become deeply united
また 躓いて 転がって それでも砕けない
Once again stumbling, rolling, still won’t break into pieces
魂の色は 何色ですか
The color of the soul, what color is it?
ただ 傷ついて 強がって それでも見つけたいよ
Just wounded, putting on a brave front, but I still want to find it
魂のカタチ 確かめてるよ
The shape of the soul, I’m confirming it
深い地の底で一人
Down in the depths of the ground, alone
扉と鍵を探す
Searching for a door and a key
おとぎ話は ほら
The fairy tale, see
泡の様に全部消えて
All disappears like bubbles
葛藤、残像だけ
Just emotional conflict and residual images
次の 頁へ
On to the next page
伸びてく枝葉が分かれて
A stretching tree limb branches off
それぞれの道を行く
Each going off on its own path
寂しい思い出だけが強く根を張ってる
Just lonely memories are firmly rooted
まだ 貫いて 失って それでも挫けない
Still standing firm, losing sight of things, but I won’t give up
心はどこに 器はどこに
Where is the heart, where is the vessel?
ただ 残されて 抜け落ちて それでも伝えたいよ
Even if I’m left behind, slipped through the cracks, I still want to pass along
魂の日々を 魂の意志を ずっと
The days of the soul, intentions of the soul, forever
魂の色は
The color of the soul,
何色ですか
what color is it?
赤色ですか
Is it red,
青色ですか
is it blue?
魂の色は 何色ですか
The color of the soul, what color is it?
透明な過去に 不透明な明日に
To a transparent past, to an opaque tomorrow
生きるあなたは 何色ですか
You who are living, what color are you?
また 躓いて 転がって それでも砕けない
Once again stumbling, rolling, still won’t break into pieces
魂の色は 何色ですか
The color of the soul, what color is it?
ただ 傷ついて 強がって それでも見つけたいよ
Just wounded, putting on a brave front, but I still want to find it
魂のカタチ 確かめてるよ
The shape of the soul, I’m confirming it
確かめてるよ
I'm confirming it
ずっと
Forever
Woah...
NEW 3D OUTFIT?!
≪ReCOLOR≫ Hakos Baelz Birthday Live 2026